

+91 9700474780

shivashankar.chatla@gmail.com

8

https://www.behance.net/chatlasharan

About me

My self Shivashankar Passionate about graphic design and visualisation. Currently working in Tech Mahindra as Sr. Creative designer.

As a creative designer my role and responsibilities is to create co laterals from scratch.

Education

GOVT School of Education 1999 Ideal Junior College 2004

Skills

- 2D Rigging and animation.
- Creativity.
- Artistic talent.
- Attention to detail.
- Ability to work under pressure.
- Ability to meet tight deadlines.
- Team work.
- Branding.
- Print and Digital

Softwares

An Adobe Animate

Ai Adobe Illustrator

Ps Adobe Photoshop

Adobe InDesign

Ae Adobe After Effects

Xd Adobe XD

Office 365

Operating System





Interests

Skeching

Photography

Painting

Music

Experience

Sr. Graphic Designer

Tech Mahindra June 2017 - Till now

Graphic Designer

Freelance May 2016 to June 2017

Sr. 2D Flash Animator

Mag Arts Creation July 2015 - May 2016

Graphic Designer

Freelance Aug 2013 to July 2015

Sr. 2D Flash Animator

Objectone information systems Nov 2012 to Aug 2013

2D Flash Animator

Freelance Oct 2011 to Nov 2012

Graphic Designer

Next Education Pvt Ltd May 2010 to Sep 2011

2D Flash Animator

Data Quest International Entertainment Pvt Ltd Jul 2008 to Apr 2010

Summary

Overall 8+ years of total experience in 2D animation and also Graphic design Industry. I am technically sound and have hands on experience in working with all tools used for developments, such as Animate, Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, After Effects, Sound Forge, and have ability to adapt new tools and technologies that might be client-specific. Iam a good team player, efficient planning, and co-ordination.